my good friend josephine gobo was arrested last night for protesting the gestapo in minneapolis
but that's not what this video is about this video is about ops god damn this last month has
been nothing but fucking ops either meant to divide or meant to unite under a false pretense
and i think this is like that moment you know where you know daddy sits all the children down
and explains to them that uh real hard work and revolution does not come with the camera
crew sometimes and i'll just use patriotism as an example when americans think of patriotism
they think of patchy helicopters going into afghanistan and slaughtering a village full of
brown people with mark walberg or jake gyllenhaal that's not patriotism patriotism is not glamorous
this is what patriotism looks like average ass americans or average ass people living in this
country fighting masked armed child traffickers trained by a foreign government who are kidnapping
people off the streets that's patriotism revolutionaries are operating in the shadows
doing the grind on the streets with no cameras rolling in the words of my good friend esty of
the brown berets don't chase after shiny objects whether they are meant to divide or whether they
are meant to unite under a false too good to be true pretense the revolution is going to be hard it's
going to be complicated it's going to have failures it's going to have successes it's going to be messy
it's going to be chaotic it's not a corporation doesn't have a huge budget it's going to be broke
the revolution is going to be broke okay if you are looking for a savior galloping in on a
white horse with armor looking sexy it's not going to happen revolution is going to be ugly and
disorganized that being said i want you to listen to this message from esti from the brown berets in
southern california and my boss bunchy carter minister of defense for the black panther party
listen to what they're saying it has wisdom it's not glamorous but it has wisdom and let's just dump
cold water on these division tactics if you hear anybody claiming to be a revolutionary or belonging to
a revolutionary organization that was inspired by some movement in the 1960s and they start spewing
some bullshit about division or taking care of our own like the john brown club that just started
telling their members down in virginia that we're not going to be helping black and brown people yeah
that happened the john brown club started telling their members that they are not going to be helping
black and brown people that they're going to start taking care of their own white people let me remind
you that your people are poor people and all of us are fucking poor your people are not white people
your people are poor people that's the only common denominator that all of us share that
fucking matters it's been a frustrating fucking month but watch this video as always love you fam
good morning this is capitana esti here with an important official statement from the brown beret
organization we the brown berets standing on wavering solidarity with our native black white allies any
and all oppressed people that being said we stand with the american indian movement the black panthers
and all our other comrades ready to join the intercommunal council we strive for the liberation
sovereignty of all native people but we realize our struggles are very interconnected we stand with
all the people who are struggling victims of this corrupt systemic violence our stance is uncompromising
voting is pointless against special interests and increasingly gruesome tactics used by imperialist forces
so we the brown berets commit ourselves to the lifelong work of decolonizing this is only attainable through
discipline daily study and revolutionary education we do this for our communities and future generations
we are the protectors of our circle we teach self-defense courses to our members and the community for free
because we realize a long time ago nobody is coming to save us we have a saying that goes
only the people can save the people unfortunately not all people who are calling themselves brown berets
believe in these concepts yet this is not symbolic work and we the brown beret organization really do
practice what we preach we accept only those who demonstrate true integrity commitment and dedication to
this movement we stand in solidarity with the intercommunal council made to serve the people by the
the people may our actions contribute to impactful change for generations to come we look forward to
working hard together remember liberation is non-negotiable all power to the people
my father used to tell me when i was young he was like hey man look he said let me ask you a question
he said if you ever saw something that you wanted to punch a hole in your right where would you hit it
i said i probably hit it where it's the weakest the way is the weak where is it the weakest it's the
weakest where it's not solid that's where it's the weakest and right now what's happening is the imperialists
are doing a wonderful job of creating a lot of not solid places within the armor of the people
because organizations like ours are the armor of the people that's why we do what we do to protect
their right to exist in the way that they see fit that's why we do it but it's impossible to do that
with any effective with any true effectiveness um when we're not able to find common ground
like simple common ground and the differences between us are going to be exaggerated
they're going to be exaggerated because that is the quickest way to to to to root that division
within people you you'll do it yourself if they can make you believe in the differences enough
they won't even have to do it there won't be a need for cointel pro all the way live we don't have to
do that all we got to do is remind them that they not like them all we got to do is remind them that
their berets are brown and there's a black all we got to do is remind them that he's fighting for
palestine but it's way over there they're fighting about something right here all we got to do
is be like well hell we give the natives hell of money because he knows all of that y'all don't get
out of that right and as long as they can continue to tell us this and we continue to buy it i'm gonna
look at dakota and be like i mean he cool but i'll look at mark and doc and say i mean they
cool but i look at mohams and i look at and see and i think i mean they cool but
and as long as that butt hangs in the air falls as long as the butt hangs in there
there are going to be questions and as long as the questions is this exist there can't be true
solidarity and where there's no true solidarity they will find the weakness in the armor of the
people and find a way to pierce that at every single turn so when you make people quick i'll just be
honest about something when you have people i'm not even on social media and in the last two weeks
i've been sitting the same link a hundred times by different people hey this y'all man this your man
this what y'all doing and you know what i said because i'm very aware of the division tactics being
played i don't know what you mean i call him and talk to him because anything beyond that is really none of
your business if you were not come back we can't afford to jeopardize strategy for high idiots like
oh my god i'm trying to find a way to say this without saying something i don't need to say okay
i'll put it this way there are many things that are moving between the intercommunal people's
core between the paper between all the there are plenty of things that are moving you know when the
movement gets halted whenever one of those videos appear hey did you see this now for the next 45
minutes everybody and their mom is talking about this video and if it's if you think it's only 45
minutes that they're talking about it that's only the 45 minutes that you see you don't get to see
the other two hours that they're wasting on it talking to their friend who don't know you from adam
who wouldn't know a black path if they walked up and slapped him in the face who wouldn't like
what are we doing really why are we giving energy to division we're feeding the we're feeding the machine
exactly what it wants so now when i go to the east coast i gotta watch my back for people that call
they self the same thing i call myself why that should never be the case eldridge cleaver dead
eldridge cleaver's dead you understand me we can't we can't allow what happened then
to impact what we're building now we saw what happened with wild bill o'neill
it won't be another one of them not on i watch it won't but that can only happen if we let if we if we
implore all of the other people who call themselves revolutionaries to invest in solidarity over
division that's the only way we can do it that's the only way i don't care if you call yourself black
panther i don't care you call yourself a black beagle i don't care what it is i don't care to
me the animal means nothing this and this mean more than everything so the easiest way to deal with it
in my personal opinion let the ride pardon my french i do apologize for i try my best not to
do this when i'm in front of cameras talking to people but you got to let that ride because all
of it's gonna play itself out if you paying close enough attention the last two weeks you sent all
these messages to ask all these questions and now it's sorted itself out and i kept telling people
don't worry about it it'll take care of itself trust me and it did what we're building means more
than what they're trying to destroy and as long as we know that we can't lose